（忆往昔）
你好 迪恩 你到底想要什么
Hello, Dean. what is it you want?
路西法的牢笼
Lucifer's cage.
萨姆的灵魂被困在里面了
Sam's soul is stuck in that box.
抹去地狱的记忆我办不到
Can't erase Sam's hell.
但我可以将它隔离在屏障之外
But I can put it behind a wall.
那些记忆可谓十分不愉快
Nasty, those memories.
你不会想知道那些记忆会如何影响他
You don't want to know what they'll do to him.
死亡骑士说他能建一个屏障
Death said he can put up a wall.
地狱的一切你都会忘记
You wouldn't remember hell.
- 不要这样做 - 别碰这个屏障
- Don't do this. - Don't scratch the wall.
迪恩 你本该告诉我的
You should have told me, Dean.
你本来就不该知道
You weren't supposed to know.
我曾经干的好事儿
What I did?
对鲍比 对你
To Bobby? To you?
我当然应该知道
Of course I should know.
萨姆 死亡骑士并不只是
Sam, death didn't just.
把你灵魂放回来 懂吗
shove your soul back in, okay?
他在你和你遗忘的那些事中间
He put up the great wall of Sam.
建立起了一道「萨姆之墙」
between you and the things that you don't remember.
你最好是相信我
And trust me when I say.
你不记得的那些事能杀死你
that the things you don't know could kill you.
我没在说笑
That's not a joke.
但我得弥补过失
But I have to set things right.
所以我得知道 我到底做了什么
So I need to know what I did.
可你不知道那有多危险
But you don't know how dangerous that could be.
我警告过你不要把灵魂放回他体内
I warned you not to put that thing back inside him.
那我应该怎么做
What was I supposed to do?
我来告诉你当我碰到他灵魂时是什么感觉
Let me tell you what his soul felt like when I touched it.
就像是被活剥了一样 迪恩
Like it had been skinned alive, Dean.
如果你想要杀了你弟弟
If you wanted to kill your brother,
你应该给他个痛快
you should have done it outright.
（如今）
（布里斯托尔 罗德岛 一年前）
- 你还好吧 - 没事
- You okay? - Yeah.
胳膊怎么样了
How's the arm?
可以坚持到我们出城
It'll hold till we get out of town.
别弄到大出血 行吗
Just don't bleed out, all right?
嗯 希望如此
Yeah, well, that's the plan.
有警察
Cop.
晚上好 警官
Evening, deputy.
洛克探员 维南探员
Agent Roark, agent Wynand,
请先下车好吗
mind stepping out of the van a moment?
我们正要去办公室 有什么事吗
We're just on our way to the office. Everything okay?
有 我联系不到多布斯治安官
No. I can't get sheriff Dobbs on the phone.
我联系不到任何人
I can't get anyone!
我们之前和多布斯联系过 也许他刚好…
We spoke to Dobbs earlier. Maybe he's just, uh …
那是血吗
Is that blood?
听着 别这么大火气
Hey, look, there's no need to get riled.
- 你们俩跟我走一趟吧 - 好吧
- You're coming with me. - All right.
我们会跟在你后边
We'll follow you back.
我不这么认为
I don't think so.
坐我的车 否则就拘捕你们
Get in my car, or you're under arrest.
你要逮捕两名联邦探员吗
You're gonna arrest two federal agents?
真的吗
Really?
祝你晚上愉快
Have a good night.
如果你觉得
If you think …
喂喂 慢着
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, just hold …
你不觉得也许我们该用更冷静的方法
You think there were maybe calmer ways.
来解决这事儿吗
we could have done all that?
管他的呢
Do we care?
我们走吧
Let's go.
[邪恶力量 第6季第13集]
有消息称
Sources said.
检察官正在决定
prosecutors were getting closer to a decision.
是否要起诉这名演员
on whether to charge the actor.
但他们坚决否认诉讼…
But they adamantly denied that any prosecution was in any…
你在看什么呢
What are you watching?
了解下时事 所以…
Just trying to catch up. So…
过去一年梅尔·吉布森真的是变化很大啊
Mel·Gibson really took a turn this past year, huh?
或者他是被附身了
Or he's possessed.
真的 考虑下
Seriously, think about it.
我刚和鲍比通了电话
So, I just got off the blower with Bobby.
哦 是吗
Oh, yeah?
你有什么其他线索吗 关于万物之母
You got anything else on this, uh, "Mother of all" thing?
没有 都不可靠
Uh, no, nothing solid.
他说目前很安静
He says it's quiet.
普通的安静还是暴风雨前的宁静
Quiet like quiet or quiet like too quiet?
啥时候「普通」过
When is it ever just quiet?
也是
Right.
怎么了
What?
这些是什么 坐标吗 谁发你的
What are these, coordinates? Who's it from?
我也不知道
I have no idea.
怎么样了
Well?
是布里斯托尔的罗德岛
Uh, Bristol, Rhode Island,
该地上周有三个女人失踪
where three women disappeared in the last week.
显然受害者像是凭空消失了一样
Apparently, the, uh, victims seemed to vanish into thin air.
可能是有蹊跷 到底是谁发的信息
Could be something. Who's the text from?
我不知道 一直在给我发
I don't know. It just kept ringing.
- 到底几个意思 - 会不会是别的猎魔人
- What's that about? - Could be another hunter.
在寻求支援 丢给我俩一个案子
looking for backup, throwing us a case?
天知道我见过多少猎魔人
Who knows how many hunters I even met,
再我和坎贝尔家的人一起猎魔的时候
working with the Campbells, you know?
但我觉得我们应该去
But I think we should go.
等下 就这么放下手头的事过去啊
Whoa, wait. We're just gonna drop everything?
老哥 两分钟前 你什么事也没做
Dude, two minutes ago, you weren't doing anything.
你从一个神秘人那
You got mysterious coordinates.
收到了个通向一个神秘地方的
from a mysterious Mr."X, "
神秘的坐标
leading to a mysterious town?
你不觉得这太诡异了吗
That doesn't throw up red flags to you?
我也不知道 也许吧
I don't know. Maybe.
但那并不意味着我们可以
But that doesn't mean we.
对那些失踪的女孩坐视不理
can just ignore a bunch of missing girls.
对吧
Right?
好吧 我们去看看
Okay. We'll check it out.
但如果事情变得很蹊跷
But if things get squirrelly,
我们就不管了 好吗
we dump out, okay?
行
Yeah.
怎么了
What?
没什么
Nothing.
那怪物喜欢黑发的女人哎
Well, freak's got a type … brunettes.
这个有点野性
This one's got a little bit of a wild side.
看她的眼神儿 萨姆
It's all in the eyes, Sam.
看到没
See it?
好吧 除了你那点深刻的洞悉
All right, well, aside from your little deep insight there,
这些女人根本没有共同点
these women actually have nothing in common,
不同的工作 不同的朋友圈
different jobs, different friends,
什么都不一样
different everything.
有什么联系呢
So, what's the connection?
我也不知道 你来查清楚吧
I don't know. Why don't you figure that out?
我要去厕所喽
I'm gonna go hit the Poop Deck.
是洛克探员吗
Agent Roark?
能再见到你很高兴
It's good to see you again.
确实
It is.
你记得我丈夫吗
Oh, you remember my husband?
是的
Right.
- 唐 - 当然当然 你好
- Don. - Of course, right. Um, hi.
那么
So…
你回来是因为那个又开始了吗
So, you're back 'cause it started again, right?
那些失踪事件
The disappearances?
是的是的 没错
Uh, yeah. Yeah, right.
如果你们俩听到什么消息
Um…So, if either of you two hear anything,
请通知我
please let me know.
你的搭档呢
Where's your partner?
秃头的大家伙
The big bald guy?
维南探员 对吧
Agent Wynand, right?
- 维南探员 当然 - 在性瘾康复治疗
- Agent Wynand, of course. Well… - Sex rehab.
听说过恋物癖吧
Yeah, you've heard of plushies, right?
这位 这位是我的新搭档
This is, uh … this is my new partner.
你好 幸会
Hi. Pleasure.
你好 你好
How you doing? Hi.
那么 探员 我们该
Uh, so, agent, we should, uh.
是的是的 当然
Yeah. Yeah, of course.
当然 和你聊天很高兴 洛克探员
Of course. Uh, nice chatting with you, agent Roark.
我也是
You too.
铐住我吧
Cuff me.
咋回事
What was that?
她看你那眼神儿也太饥渴了吧
She just cougar-eyed you.
我想萨穆埃尔和我来这里办过案子
I think Samuel and I have worked a case in this town.
不用想了 就是
You think?
来 我们赶紧撤把
Come on. Let's get the hell out of here.
快点 咱赶紧走行吗
Hey, come on. Hop to, would you?
我们不能走 迪恩
We can't go, Dean.
当然能走
Uh, yeah, we can.
不 听着 五个男人在一年前失踪了
No, listen … five guys went missing a year ago.
尸体下落不明
They never found the bodies.
我和萨穆埃尔肯定就是
I mean, that's got to be the job.
来查这件案子的 对吧
me and Samuel worked, right?
对极了 那又如何
Great. What difference does it make?
一年前五个男人失踪了
A year ago, five guys go missing,
现在呢 突然这些女人也失踪了
And … and now suddenly all these women go missing.
有什么鬼怪在作祟
Something's here.
所以 要么我们没消灭它
So either we just didn't stop it,
要么就以为消灭了 其实没有
or we only thought we did.
好吧 但是为啥后来变了性别
Okay, but why the gender bend, huh?
先是男人 现在是女人
First it's dudes. Now it's chicks?
犯罪模式完全不同
That's a totally different M.O.
我不知道 鬼知道啊
I don't know. Who knows?
问题是 那东西还在这里
The point is, something's still here.
很好 打给鲍比 他能处理这事儿
Great. Well, call Bobby. He can deal with it.
为什么 我们自己也能处理啊
Why? We can deal with it.
你开玩笑吧
Are you serious?
萨姆 猎魔人不能
Sam, there is a reason.
重复出现在同一个地方是有原因的
that hunters don't hit the same town over again …
因为我们习惯一走了之 留下堆烂摊子
'cause we have a habit of leaving messes behind.
- 好吧 我承认 - 爸爸的规矩之一
- Right. I agree. - One of dad's rules …
同一个厕所不能去两次
you never use the same crapper twice.
每个人都会重复使用同一个厕所
Everyone uses the same crapper twice.
除了我们
Not us.
你知道我啥意思
You know what I mean.
好吧 听着
Okay, look …
因为我 那个东西还在作恶 对吧
this creature is still walking around 'cause of me, right?
是我放走它的
I mean, I let it go.
爸爸还说过 要「善始善终」
Dad also said, "you finish what you start."
好吧 我懂了
Okay, I get it.
- 是吗 - 是的
- Do you? - Yes.
你害怕我会随着记忆顺藤摸瓜
You're afraid I'll stroll down memory lane.
然后狠狠毁掉我脑子里的屏障
and I'll kick this wall in my head so hard,
地狱的记忆就会破口而出 对吧
hell comes flooding through, right?
然后我一下子就精神崩溃了什么的
And then all of a sudden, I'm some drooling mess on the floor.
这可不是开玩笑
It's not a joke.
好啦 我知道
Okay. I know.
听着 现在这里发生的一切
But listen … what's happening here right now …
都是因为我搞砸了
it's because I messed up somehow,
而且后果还很严重
in some big way.
每一个失踪的人 每一个死去的人
So every person who gets taken, every person who dies …
都是我害的
that's on me.
我必须阻止这一切
I have to stop it.
换做是你也会这么做
And you'd do the same thing.
好吧
All right.
我去查那些黑发姑娘
I'll follow up with the brunettes.
你去警察那里打探一下
You see what you get from the cops.
你和尼科尔做了很久的室友
So, you and Nicole were roommates for a long time.
从大学开始 但我们一直是最好的朋友
Since college, but we've been best friends forever.
这个事情太离奇了
This whole thing's really surreal.
你们的调查有进展吗 还是
Are you any closer to finding her, or…?
我们会尽最大的努力
We're doing everything we can.
尼科尔失踪那晚 你和她在一起
Now, you were with Nicole the night she went missing.
她说什么了吗
Did she say anything?
没有
Nothing.
正如我给警察说的那样
It's like I told the cops …
我也希望能提供些线索
I wish there was something.
这个哪儿来的
Where'd you get this?
一个联邦探员给尼科尔的
Oh, Nicole got that from that FBI guy.
洛克探员
Agent Roark.
大概 这么高
About … about yea high?
对 就是他
Yeah, that was him.
去年的失踪者之一
One of the men that disappeared last year.
住在我们这栋楼里
lived in our building.
嗯
Right.
所以洛克探员问了我们些
So agent Roark was asking us.
关于那个案子的问题 我猜
all questions about it, I guess.
你猜
You guess?
那 他来过这里
So he … he came by here?
对 来过几次
Oh, he came by a few times.
是嘛
Did he?
来
To, uh…
和尼科尔谈话
speak to Nicole.
对
Right.
你觉得
And how would you…
他们是什么关系
characterize their relationship?
关系 不 他们没有
Relationship? No, they weren't having a …
就是 说话的语气啊
Just the … the … the tone.
谈话的性质啊
or the nature of their conversation.
声音很大
Well…loud.
还有
And…
有活力
athletic.
站住
Hold it right there!
站住别动
Stop right there!
举起手来
Hands where I can see them!
上警车 不然就逮捕你们
Get in my car, or you're under arrest.
听着 长官 不
Look … no, sir.
请等一下
Please just hold on for a second.
这是一场误会
There's been a misunderstanding here.
兄弟 你真是傻逼到家了
Man, you are dumb as a sack of hair …
干了坏事还自己送上门来
coming back here after what you did?
听着 这是一场误会
Look, there's been a misunderstanding here.
你根本不是个探员
You are not a damn agent, okay?
- 联邦调查局压根不知道你 - 听着
- The FBI never heard of you. - Just listen.
尸体在哪里
Where are the bodies?
母亲们想要安葬自己的亲人
Mothers want to bury their loved ones.
我不知道
I don't know.
多布斯治安官呢
Where's sheriff Dobbs?
我不知道
I don't know.
你离开这里时 浑身是血
You run out of town soaked in blood …
为了逃跑 还把我的头打伤
Oh, and you bash my brains in to do it …
你还妄想让我相信你
and you really expect me to buy that?
我什么都不记得了 你相信吗
Look, would you believe that I don't remember anything?
不
No.
但愿法官能相信你的鬼话
But good luck selling it to the judge.
我的丈夫出了什么事
What happened to my husband?
我也不知道
Look, I-I don't know.
别骗我
Don't lie to me.
我知道你是谁 萨姆
I know who you are, Sam.
我知道你是干什么的
I know what you do.
什么
What?
你真知道
You do?
让我搞搞清楚 你们不是联调局的人
Let me get this straight … you're not feds.
你们是猎魔人
You actually hunt things.
- 我们知道这听起来很离奇 - 我看未必
- We know how it sounds. - I'm not sure you do.
罗伊 你到过事发现场
You saw those crime scenes, Roy.
你真觉得是个人类带走那些人的吗
You really think something human could have taken those guys?
你说的那些是天方夜谭
What you're saying … it's impossible.
对不起 我不明白
You know, I'm sorry, I-I don't understand.
这关她什么事儿
what she's got to do with any of this.
她是我的妻子
She's my wife.
她和我一起在警局工作
She works with me at the sheriff's station.
你告诉我的事情 也要告诉她
You tell something like this to me, you tell it to her, too.
好吧 你们需要我们做什么
All right, what do you need us to do?
你的丈夫 他是那个治安官
Your husband … he's the sheriff.
曾经是 直到他失踪
Was the sheriff, until he vanished…
然后你也失踪了
and you vanished.
我该怎么想
What was I supposed to think?
那东西抓走了他 还是你杀了他
T-that thing got him, or that you killed him?
我只想知道到底是怎么回事
I just want to know what happened.
我也想知道 相信我
So do I. Believe me.
我身上发生了一些事情
Something happened to me.
我不记得我来过这里
I have no memory of being here, ever.
这算什么 演《我们的日子》（NBC早期电视剧）吗
What is this, "Days of our lives"?
你是想告诉我 你得了失忆症么
You're telling me you have some sort of amnesia?
如果我知道这些事情
If I knew any of this,
我还会主动跑来警局送死吗
would I have stepped foot into this station?
对不起
I'm sorry.
我都不知道你叫什么
I-I don't even know your name.
如果这是某种游戏
If this is some sort of a game,
你要么是聪明绝顶 要么是愚蠢至极
you're either incredibly clever or incredibly stupid.
我说的是实话
I'm telling the truth.
听我说
Look…
我真不知道你丈夫出了什么事
I don't know what happened to your husband.
但是我能找出真相
But I can find out.
怎么做
How?
若你真的了解我 你就知道这是我的工作
If you really know me, then you know that's my job.
你真的不记得了
You really don't remember?
真的不记得了
No. I really don't.
我是布伦娜·多布斯
I'm Brenna Dobbs.
布伦娜
Brenna…
你丈夫的事 我深表遗憾
…I'm sorry about what happened to your husband.
但我能找出真相
But I can find answers…
可困在这里 我束手无策
just not from in here.
出来 帮我找点绳子
Come on. Help me find some rope.
想要伪装成越狱的样子
If it's gonna look like a break-out,
你得把我绑起来
you're gonna need to tie me up.
怎样啊
What?
唐 不是时间越久 东西就越好
The boxed stuff doesn't get better with age, Don.
是我 萨姆
Hey, Sam.
再次逃亡的滋味怎么样
So, how does it feel to be a fugitive again?
真不想说「不听老哥言」
Hate to say "I told you so."
你就喜欢说「不听老哥言」
You love to say "I told you so."
你说对了 我确实喜欢说「不听老哥言」
Actually, you're right … I do love to say "I told you so."
我在野性妞儿身上发现了线索
So, I found something on, uh, "Crazy eyes McGee."
原来你俩是旧相识
Turns out you two knew each other.
啥
What?
我是说性关系 我刚和她室友谈过
Biblically. I just spoke to her roommate.
我得说 老弟你真是风流债满天下
I got to say, man … you really got around.
有没有灵魂都如此 我真是服了
I mean, soulless or not I'm actually kind of impressed.
又一个人失踪了
Missing person … another one.
好的 我去 你呆在这里
Okay, all right. I'll go. You stay.
好吧
Yeah. Fine.
- 萨姆 - 咋啦
- Sam? - What?
乖乖呆在这里
Stay here.
知道啦 快去
Fine! Go!
感谢您抽空配合
Listen, thank you for your time.
我们在调查
We're on it.
好的 谢谢
Yeah. Thanks.
我是萨姆 请留言
This is Sam. Leave a message.
萨姆 接电话 该死的
Sam, answer the phone, damn it.
我找到失踪女孩之间的联系了
I found the connection between the missing chicks.
她们都和同一个家伙上过床
They all banged the same dude …
你
You.
是你 萨姆
It's you, Sam.
短信 受害者 所有这一切
The texts, the victims, all of it …
都是为你而设的陷阱
It's a trap for you.
回我电话
Call me back.
不好意思 不好意思
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
你不能来这里
You can't be here!
好的 请听我说
Okay, p-please just listen.
黛比·哈里斯是怎么回事
What happened to Debbie Harris?
黛比
Debbie?
我放你出来 她就失踪了
I let you out, and she's just gone.
你认为是我做的
And y-you think I did something to her?
我不知道该怎么想
I don't know what to think.
听着 我需要你的帮助
Look, um, I need your help.
你开玩笑吧
Are you kidding?
我需要你丈夫整理的有关
I need the case files that your husband made.
去年失踪案的文件
about the disappearances last year.
去警察局找
So go to the station and find it.
不在那里
It's not there.
我溜进去找了 文件不见了
I broke in and I looked, and it's gone.
我也知道是谁拿的
And I have a theory about who might have it.
听着 我们的目的一致 布伦娜
Look, we both want the same thing here, Brenna.
我保证
I promise.
我们想弄明白去年发生了什么
We want to find out what happened last year,
我们也想阻止现在发生的事情
and we want to stop what's happening right now.
那些文件在楼上
The file's upstairs.
我马上就回来
I'll be right back.
走吧
Let's go!
你们一直都在旅行吗
So, you guys just travel all the time?
轻装上阵 常年奔波
I mean, you just pick up and go?
不会很艰难吗
Doesn't that get hard?
年轻时不算困难 觉得挺棒的
Not when you're young … it's great.
一旦有了家庭 是有点艰难
Once you got a family, it's a little tougher.
迪恩娜怀孕的时候
Deanna got pregnant,
我们手足无措
and we didn't know what we were gonna do.
但是玛丽
But Mary was…
是上帝的恩赐
she was a blessing.
车库里面还有
There's more in the garage.
你坐着 我去拿
Ah, listen, you sit. I'll get it.
他想念她
He misses her.
你们至少还有彼此相互依靠
You know, at least you two have each other.
我小时候和萨穆埃尔相处不多
Well, Samuel wasn't really around when I was a kid.
我和他更多的是工作上的往来
We have more of a, uh, business relationship.
你们还有其他的家人吗
Uh, do you have any other family?
家人只会拖后腿
Family just slows you down.
萨姆
Sam?
Sam?!
你还好吧
You all right?
很好 我没事
Yeah. Yeah.
好吧 开始看文件吧
Um…All right, let's see what you have.
最大可能 这东西来自阿拉克尼（希神）
Best guess … it came from an Arachne.
- 你见过吗 - 没人见过
- You ever seen one? - No one has …
2000年以来 没人在克里特岛之外见过
Not outside of crete, not for about 2, 000 years.
那关于他们有什么记载
Then what do we even know about them?
啥都没
Zip.
只有一些猜测
Just a bunch of guesses.
和一个希腊瓶饰上的模糊画像
and a blurry picture on the side of a greek vase.
耶
Yeah!
嘿 船长
Yo ho, sea captain.
那我们不知道怎么杀死这个东西 是吧
So, I gather we got no clue how to kill this thing, huh?
咱们尽力吧 看能不能歪打正着
I guess we just go at it till something sticks.
好极了 至少我知道它大概在哪里
Well, great, I got an idea of where it might be, at least.
迄今为止 受害者都是30岁左右的男子
So far, all the vics have been men in their 30s,
失踪地点都在半径2英里内
and they've all gone missing within a 2-mile radius.
所以我们就去乱找一通吗
So we just get out and kick bushes.
那纯是浪费时间
No, that'd be a waste of time.
我是说 这片都是郊区
I mean, it's all suburban sprawl …
至少几百栋房子
hundreds of houses, at least.
根本是大海捞针
It could be anywhere.
- 孤柳公园 - 是的
- Lonely pines park. - Yeah.
我看不如让这个东西来找我们
I say we make this thing come to us.
我们怎么做
How do we do that?
布伦娜 如果我
Hey, um, Brenna, do you mind if I …
借走这些文件几个小时 你不介意吧
If I, um, borrow all this stuff for a couple hours?
好的
Um, okay, I guess.
你真的不记得罗伊了 是吗
You really don't remember Roy, do you?
他是个好人
He was a good man.
我已经接受了他的死
I've made peace that he's dead.
真的
I have.
但我想知道发生了什么
But I just want to know what happened.
我肯定他死得英勇
I'm sure he died a hero.
萨姆 接电话 该死的
Sam, answer the phone, damn it.
我找到失踪小妞之间的联系了
I found the connection between the missing chicks.
她们都和同一个家伙上过床
They all banged the same dude …
你
You.
是你 萨姆
It's you, Sam.
短信 受害者 所有这一切
The texts, the victims, all of it …
都是为你而设的陷阱
it's a trap for you.
回我电话
Call me back.
我差点开枪
I almost shot you…
第二次了
again.
搞什么飞机
What the hell?
我估摸着你会来和她谈话
I figured you'd come and talk to her.
我让你呆家里的 老弟
I told you to stay home, man.
听到我的留言了吗
Did you get my message?
快点 你不能在这儿呆着了 走吧
Come on. We got to get you out of here. Let's go.
我们知道这个怪物
We do know that this is a monster.
拇指行动自如
with a apposable thumb.
还有短信包月
and unlimited text messaging,
而且还知道它特别想杀了你
and we know that it wants to kill you specifically.
没落什么吧
Does that about cover it?
是个阿拉克尼
It's an Arachne.
什么东东
A what?
我记起来了
I remembered.
你记起来了
You remembered?
抱歉
Y… I'm sorry.
你还记起什么了
Uh, what else have you remembered?
别紧张好吗 和地狱无关
Don't worry, all right? I-it's nothing to do with hell.
- 目前而已 - 迪恩 我能咋办
- Uh-huh. Not yet, anyway. - What can I do, Dean?
记忆开始涌现 懂吗
The stuff is just starting to come back, all right?
也许这是自然现象
Maybe it's natural.
- 我们要离开这 - 不行
- We're leaving. - No, we can't.
我们不是世上唯一的猎魔人 好吗
We are not the only hunters on the planet, okay?
我们可以给鲍比电话
We can call Bobby.
- 他和鲁弗斯可以搞定这一切 - 怎么搞定
- He and rufus could come and wrap this up. - How?
如你所说 它可能是任何人
Like you said, it could be anybody,
而我们一点线索都没
and we got jack for leads.
- 我们知道它恨死你了 - 我知道是谁干的
- We know that it hates you. - I know who did this.
我只是记不起来了
I just … I can't remember.
我想你不知道这事的危险性 萨姆
I don't think you get the risk here, Sam.
- 我知道 - 真的吗
- Yes, I do. - Really?
你知不知道你每次去碰那个屏障
You get that every time you scratch that wall,
你就是在玩儿命啊
that you are playing russian roulette?
迪恩 我知道你很担心 好吗
Dean, I get you're worried, okay?
我也知道你在担心什么事
And I know what you think is gonna happen.
- 但是 该来的也拦不住 - 萨姆
- But you know what? It will or it won't. - Sam …
听着 我开始想
Look, I'm starting to think.
我可能在这里做过些坏事 迪恩
that … that I might have done some bad stuff here, Dean.
所以我不管是否有危险
And so I don't care if it's dangerous.
我必须弥补我的过失
I have to set things right,
因为现在我他妈有灵魂了
'cause I got a frigging soul now,
所以我良心不安 不会拍拍屁股走人
and … and it won't let me just walk away.
我要留在这里
I'm staying here.
并且我需要你帮我
and I need you to back me up.
好吧
All right.
当然
Why not?
那么我们寻找记忆碎片去吧
Well, let's "Memento" this thing, shall we?
你回来 是因为又开始出现
So, you're back 'cause it started again, right …
失踪案了吧
the disappearances?
你们不是联调局的 你们是猎魔人
You're not feds. You actually hunt things.
你真的不记得了吗
You really don't remember?
我在野性妞儿身上发现了线索
I, uh, found something on "Crazy eyes Mcgee."
看来你们认识
Turns out you two knew each other.
那是血吗
Is that blood.
你还好吗
You okay?
没错
That's right.
一小时后孤柳公园见 谢谢 罗伊
Yeah, lonely pines park, one hour. Thanks, Roy.
好了
All right.
你确定吗
Are you sure about this?
阿拉克尼一直在捕食三十多岁的男性
The Arachne's been snacking on mid-30s guys.
我们需要符合它口味的诱饵
We need bait that fits the demo.
我太年轻 你又太老
I'm too young. You're too old.
还不是一般的老
89 and counting.
我还是认为该让罗伊了解整个计划
I still think that we should have looped Roy in on the plan.
我们得让他表现得自然点 不是吗
Do we want a credible performance, or don't we?
但如果出了问题怎么办
But what if something goes wrong?
罗伊不是小孩子 他会没事的
Roy's a big boy. He'll be fine.
相信我
Trust me.
只是 这不是我做事的风格
It's just… not the way I'm used to doing things.
明白了
Got it.
欢迎来到未来 老古董 我们走吧
Welcome to the future. Let's go.
希望它饿了
Let's hope this thing's hungry.
我们分头找
Let's split up, look for him.
不 等等 太晚了
No, no, wait. It's too late.
- 去找啊 - 他们走了 萨穆埃尔
- Let's go! - They're gone, Samuel!
听着 没事
Look … it's okay.
我开了罗伊手机上的全球定位系统
I turned on the G.P.S. on Roy's cell.
请说人话
In english, please.
无论她去哪儿 我们都能追踪到他们
We can track them back to wherever she goes.
那又如何 你把罗伊当成炮灰了是吗
So, what, Roy's just some redshirt to you,
蜘蛛饵什么的
just spider bait?
不 不 当然不是
No, no, of course not.
这是我的备用方案
This is my back-up plan.
天哪 你和它们一样冷血
My god, son, you're about as cold as they come.
你知道吗
You know that?
我们走吧
Let's go.
小可怜
Poor bastard.
救命
Help me.
我没有感觉
I can't…feel…
罗伊 她在哪儿
Roy, hey, where is she?
我猜砍掉脑袋才能杀死她
Well, I guess decapitation works.
罗伊
Roy.
你会没事的 坚持住
You're gonna be okay. Just hang in.
我们会救你
We're gonna get you some help.
如果我们马上把他送到医院
Listen, if we can get him to the hospital quick …
- 他没救了 - 什么
- He can't be helped. - What?
我不了解阿拉克尼 但我了解蜘蛛
I don't know about Arachne, but I do know about spiders.
隐居褐蛛可以一口夺命 这东西更厉害
One brown recluse bite can kill you. This thing?
看看他们 毒液在慢慢吞噬他们
Look at these guys … that poison's eating them alive.
他们只是行尸走肉而已
They're just dead men walking.
那你的意思是什么
So, what are you saying?
我说给他个干脆
I'm saying we put him out of his misery.
萨姆 别开枪
Sam…Please.
杀了这个怪物能救很多人
Killing this thing saved a lot of lives.
- 这件事情你功不可没 - 不
- We couldn't have done it without you. - No.
你是个英雄
You're a hero.
不能让尸体这样放着
We can't just leave the bodies here.
去拿汽油
Get the gasoline.
我知道怎么回事了
I know what happened.
罗伊
Roy?
我爱你
I love you.
你打算怎么对布伦娜说
What are you gonna say to Brenna?
放松 迪恩
Relax, Dean.
喂 布伦娜 我是萨姆
Hey, Brenna, it's … it's Sam.
就是打个电话看你有没有事
I'm just checking in.
当然 我可以过去
Yeah, of course I can swing by.
好 回见
Okay. Yeah. Bye.
什么事
What was that about?
她想让我过去一趟
She wants me to swing by.
为什么
For?
她说没什么大事
She said it's no big deal.
但我知道她遇到大麻烦了
I can tell she's in deep trouble.
迪恩 后门
Dean, back door.
萨姆
Sam.
那棚子里灯亮着
Light's on in the shed.
我的蜘蛛第六感告诉我 有危险啊
My spidey senses are tingling.
萨姆
Sam?
布伦娜
Brenna?
你真的对罗伊
What you did to Roy…
做过那样的事吗
is it true?
回答她 萨姆
Answer the question, Sam.
我现在看起来不错吧 萨姆
You got to admit I look good, Sam.
除了你留下的这个纪念品
Well, except for your little souvenir.
你赢了 我在你手里
You win. I'm here.
放布伦娜走
Let Brenna go.
这跟她没关系
This has nothing to do with her.
你回来之后
You come back around,
开始跟我妻子往来
start hanging out with my wife,
你还觉得这与她无关吗
and you think this has nothing to do with her?
然而 你觉得我无法妨碍你了 是吧
But then…You thought I was out of the way, right?
我得说 你他妈错大了 萨姆
I got to say, you get a hell of a lot wrong, Sam.
就像你把我丢去喂的那个怪物
Like that thing you threw me to.
你以为她是去觅食
You thought it was here to feed.
- 其实她是想繁殖 - 没错
- She was here to breed. - Yeah.
她那时正计划繁殖下一代
That thing was playing the mating game,
我想我符合她的条件
and I guess I fit her profile…
我和那些可怜鬼
Me and all those other poor bastards.
被她咬后都变成了和她一样的怪物
She bit us to turn us into what she was.
你扣动扳机的那一刻
By the time you pulled that trigger,
我就不是人了
I wasn't human.
不再是人了
Not anymore.
所以子弹杀不死我
So bullets didn't hurt me much.
火也烧不死
Oh, and neither did fire.
所以你们离开后 我们逃走了
So after you left, well, we ran.
我躲了几个月 快饿死了
Me … I hid for months, nearly starved.
你知道我怎么活下来的吗
But you know what kept me going?
每天夜里 我都梦到掐断你的脖子
Every night, I dreamed about ripping your throat out.
我不是给过你明显的提示了
I thought I was sending you a neon sign.
那个短信
The text?
抓走所有跟你上过床的女孩
Taking all those girls you screwed?
我一直在提醒你
I was kicking so much sand in your eye,
我就不懂你怎么就不明白
I couldn't figure out why you weren't getting it!
后来布伦娜说你大脑受到创伤
Then Bren tells me you've got brain damage.
真是太好了
It's just too good.
罗伊 他们在哪儿
Where are they, Roy …
那些女人在哪儿
The women?
随风消散了
Scattered…in the wind.
他们现在跟我一样
They're like me now.
你杀了一个怪物 却制造了更多
You killed one monster, you made so many more.
恭喜你
Congratulations.
现在的问题是 我是杀了你
The only question is, do I kill you…
还是转变你
…or turn you?
不 罗伊 不要
No! Roy, stop!
布伦娜
Brenna…
对不起
Look, I am so sorry.
布伦娜 我…
Brenna, I-I mean, I…
你还好吗
You okay?
你是对的
You were right.
我们不该回来这里
We shouldn't have come back here.
你确实杀死了蜘蛛侠
Well, you did kill the spider man.
你是说 我做的那些都是好事
So, you're suggesting what I did back there was a good thing?
- 我是说 - 什么
- I'm just saying … - What?
萨姆 你得明白
Sam, y-y-you got to understand.
去年的那些烂事
that all that crap last year …
全部的事都与你无关
All of it … none of it was you.
我们就说清楚吧
Let's be crystal clear, okay?
是我的错
It was me.
你想吃点什么
Well, can I get you anything?
怎么 你变成我的女服务生了吗
What are you now, my waitress?
我只是想让你开心点 你个贱人
I'm just trying to make you feel better. Don't be a bitch.
好吧 我没事
Yeah, I'm fine.
嗯 只是看起来还行
Yeah, you look fine.
我想说一切都会好转的
All I'm saying is everything's gonna be okay.
迪恩 我不知道
I don't know, Dean.
如果我在这里犯过错
If I did this here,
谁知道还有多少…
then who knows how many oth…
小萨姆
Sammy?
Sammy?!
小萨姆 说话啊
Sammy, talk to me!